Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - Shostakovich II [1962-1982] (Box 94)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Prelude, 2.Quartet, 3.Quintet, 4.Sonata, 5.Song, 6.Suite (EMPTY), 7.Style, 8.Symphony, 9.Tone Poem, 10.Trio Dates of materials: 1962-1982
  - Sibelius [1935-1982] (Box 94)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Ballet (EMPTY), 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata (EMPTY), 5.Chamb. Misc. (EMPTY), 6.Choral Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Comp. Wks (EMPTY), 8.Concerto, 9.Dance (EMPTY), 10.Hymn (EMPTY), 11.Incid. Music, 12.Instr. Misc., 13.Letters (EMPTY), 14.Literary (EMPTY), 15.March (EMPTY), 16.Misc., 17.Opera (EMPTY), 18.Orch. Misc., 19.Overture (EMPTY), 20.Piano Misc., 21.Quartet (EMPTY), 22.Quintet (EMPTY), 23.Romance (EMPTY), 24.Rondo (EMPTY), 25.Serenade (EMPTY), 26.Sonata, 27.Sonatina, 28.Song (EMPTY), 29.Style, 30.Suite (EMPTY), 31.Tone Poem, 32.Trio (EMPTY), 33.Variation (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1935-1982
  - Sibelius Symphony [1972-1976] (Box 94)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No. 1, 3.No. 2, 4.No. 3 (EMPTY), 5.No. 4, 6.No. 5, 7.No. 6, 8.No. 7 Dates of materials: 1972-1976
  - Smetana [1971-1978] (Box 94)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Dance; Tone Poem; Opera; Smetana; Musical Nationalism: Smetana in Bohemia; Biography; Style; Dance; Quartet) Dates of materials: 1971-1978
  - Stamitz [1969-1977] (Box 95)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Stamitz, Anton (1754-1809) (EMPTY), 2.Stamitz, Johann (1717-57) (Concerto; Symphony; Sinfonia; Trio; Stamitz, J.), 3.Stamitz, Karl (1746-1801) (Concerto; Orch. Misc., Stamitz, K.; Life and Catalogue of Works) Dates of materials: 1969-1977
  - Stockhausen [1962-1976] (Box 95)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Electronic; Choral Misc.; Piano Misc.; Stockhausen; Chamber Misc.; Style; Complete Works; Instr. Misc.; Biography; Opera; Orch. Misc., Piano Misc.; "Opera"; "Momente 1962") Dates of materials: 1962-1976
  - Strauss [1962-1991] (Box 95)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Chamb. Misc. (EMPTY), 5.Choral Misc., 6.Comp. Wks, 7.Concerto, 8.Incid. Mus., 9.Instr. Misc., 10.Letters, 11.Literary, 12.Misc., 13.Orch. Misc., 14.Piano Misc., 15.Serenade, 16.Sonata, 17.Song, 18.Style, 19.Suite, 20.Symphony, 21.Theoretical, 22.Variation Dates of materials: 1962- 1991
  - Strauss Opera [1959-1992] (Box 95)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Arabella, 2.Ariadne, 3.Capriccio, 4.Daphne, 5.Elektra, 6.Feuersnot, 7.Frau Ohne Schatten, 8.Friedenstag, 9.Guntram, 10.Helena, 11.Intermezzo, 12.Liebe, 13.Misc., 14.Rosenkavalier, 15.Salome, 16.Schweigsame Frau Dates of materials: 1959-1992
  - Strauss Tone Poem [1971-1992] (Box 95)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Don Juan, 2.Don Quixote, 3.Heldenleben, 4.MacBeth, 5.Misc., 6.Till, 7.Tod und Verklarung, 8.Zarathustra Dates of materials: 1971-1992
  - Strauss, Johann [1951-1972] (Box 96)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Struass, Johann (1825-99) (Operetta; Biography; Dance; Strauss; Misc.) Dates of materials: 1951-1972
  - Stravinsky I [1962-1981] (Box 96)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Anthem, 2.Biography, 3.Chamber Music, 4.Choral Misc., 5.Complete Works, 6.Concerto Dates of materials: 1962-1981
  - Stravinsky II [1969-1978] (Box 96)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Instr. Misc., 2.Keyboard, 3.Literary, 4.(Mass), 5.(Variation), 6.Octet, 7.Opera Dates of materials: 1969-1978
  - Stravinsky III 1982 (Box 96)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Oratorio, 2.Orch. Misc., 3.Sontata, 4.Style, 5.(Suite), 6.Symphony, 7.Tone Poem, 8.Vocal Misc. Dates of materials: 1982
  - Stravinsky Ballet [1960-1982] (Box 97)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Agon, 3.Apollon, 4.Baiser, 5.Danses Concertantes, 6.Firebird, 7.Flood, 8.Jeu des Cartes, 9.Noces, 10.Orpheus, 11.Persephone, 12.Petrouchka, 13.Sacre, 14.Scenes de Ballet Dates of materials: 1960-1982
  - Tchaikowsky I [1976-1984] (Box 97)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography, 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Chamber Misc., 6.Choral Music, 6.Complete Works Dates of materials: 1976-1984
  - Tchaikowsky II [1965-1985] (Box 97)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Concerto, 2.Dance, 3.Fantasia, 4.Hymn, 5.Impromptu, 6.Incidental Music, 7.Instr. Music, 8.Letters, 9.March, 10.Misc., 11.Nocturne, 12.Opera, 13.Oratorio, 14.Orch. Misc. Dates of materials: 1965-1985
  - Tchaikowsky III [1961-1983] (Box 97)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Overture, 2.Piano Misc., 3.Prelude, 4.Quartet, 5.Romance, 6.Sacred Music, 7.Scherzo, 8.Serenade, 9.Sextet, 10.Sonata, 11.Song, 12.Style, 13.Suite, 14.Tone Poem, 15.Trio, 16.Variation, 17.Vespers Dates of materials: 1961-1983
  - Tchaikowsky Symphony [1965-1984] (Box 98)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No. 1, 3.No. II, 4.No. III, 5.No. IV, 6.No. V, 7.No. VI, 8.No. VII Dates of materials: 1965-1984
  - Tcherpnin/Telemann [1968-1980] (Box 98)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Tcherepnin (Biography; Complete Works; Concerto; Suite; Symphony; Tcherepnin; Ballet), 2.Telemann, G.P (1681-1767) (Suite; Cantata; Oratorio; Concerto; Misc.; Opera; Suite; Organ Music; Telemann; Fantasia; Partita; Passion; Quartet; Complete Works; Sonata; Dance; Biography) Dates of materials: 1968-1980
  - Theory (Resource Book) I (Box 98)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Seventh Chords, 2.Leading-Tone 7th, 3.Secondary Sevenths, 4.Chain of 7ths, 5.Secondary Dominants, 6.Exercises, 7.9th Chords, 8.11th Chords, 9.13th Chords, 10.Pedal Point, 11.Ground Bass, 12.Altered Chords, 13.Misc., 14.Materials for Analyzation/Harmonization Dates of materials: ?
  - Theory (Resource Book) II (Box 98)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Singing, 2.Written, 3.Written Assignments, 4.Theory I, 5.Melodic Elements, 6.Rhythmic Elements, 7.Harmonic Elements, 8.Notational Elements Dates of materials: ?
  - Theory (Resource Book) III [1953-1961] (Box 99)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.(Scholarly Paper), 2.Ear Training, 3.Harmonic Dictation, 4.Keyboard, 5.Melodic Dictation, 6.Rhythmic Dictation, 7.(Minor Mode), 8.Church Modes, 9.Score-Reading, 10.(Formal Elements) Dates of materials: 1953-1961
  - Twentieth I [1986-1990] (Box 99)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Aleatoricism, 2.Atonalism, 3.Bulletism, 4.Computer, 5.Constructionism, 6.Cubism, 7.Dadaism, 8.Destructivism Dates of materials: 1986-1990
  - Twentieth II [1959-1990] (Box 99)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Electronicism Dates of materials: 1959-1990
  - Twentieth III [1963-1991] (Box 99)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Entropic Music, 2.Existentialism, 3.Expressionism, 4.Fauvism, 5.Functionalism, 6.Futurism, 8.Gebrauchsmusik, 9.Gestural Music, 10.Graphic Music, 11.Gregorianism (EMPTY), 12.Imagism, 13.Improvisation (EMPTY), 14.Instr. Explor. Dates of materials: 1963-1991
  - Twentieth IV [1980-1990] (Box 100)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Maximalism, 2.Microtonalism, 3.Minimalism, 4.Misc., 5.Multi-Media, 6.Music Concrete, 7.Nationalism (EMPTY), 8.Neo- Classicism, 9.Nihilism, 10.Orientalism, 11.Pandiatonicism, 12.Pointillism, 13.Pop Art (EMPTY), 14.Post. Impress., 15.Post-Romanticism, 16.Primitivism Dates of materials: 1980-1990
  - Twentieth V [1969-1988] (Box 100)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Satiricism, 2.Serialism, 3.Surrealism, 4.Symbolism, 5.Vorticism, 6.Modern Music, 7.Composer Dates of materials: 1969- 1988
  - Varese/Vaughan Williams [1960-1987] (Box 100)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Verese, Edgar (1885-) (Chamber Misc.; Biography; Orch. Misc.; Ballet; Style; Complete Works; Vocal Misc.; Instr. Misc.; Electronic; Varese; Vocal Misc.; Aesthetics), 2.(Vaughan Williams) (Concerto; Style; Hymn; Complete Works; Fantasia; Serenade; Symphony; Incid. Music; Suite; Song Cycle; Serenade; Cantata; Song; Instr. Misc.; Romance; Mass; Biography; Vaughan Williams; Symphony No. 5; Choral Music; Magnificat; Sonata) Dates of materials: 1960-1987
  - Variation I (Box 100)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.General, 2.Renaissance, 3.Baroqoe, 4.Classical, 5.Romantic, 6.Modern, Dates of materials: ?
  - Variation II (Box 101)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Medieval Renaissance, 2.Baroque, 3.Classical, 4.Romantic, 5.20th Century, 6.Beginning Dates of materials: ?
  - Verdi I [1969-1982] (Box 101)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Aida, 2.Alzira (EMPTY), 3.Attila, 4.Ballo in Maschero, 5.Battaglia di Legnano, 6.Biography, 7.Choral Misc., 8.Complete Works, 9.Corsaro, Il, 10.Don Carlos, 11.Due Foscari, I, 12.Ernani Dates of materials: 1969-1982
  - Verdi II [1977-1982] (Box 101)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Falstaff, 2.Forza del Destino, 3.Giorno di Regno, 4.Giovanna d'Arco, 5.Lombardi, I, 6.Luisa Miller, 7.Macbeth, 8.Masnadieri, I, 9.Mass Dates of materials: 1977-1982
  - Verdi III [1969-1981] (Box 101)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Nabucco, 3.Oberto (EMPTY), 4.Otello Dates of materials: 1969-1981
  - Verdi IV [1951-1982] (Box 102)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Rigoletto, 2.Simon Boccanegra, 3.Stiffelio, 4.Style, 5.Traviata, La, 6.Trovatore, Il, 7.Vepres Siciliennes, 8.Vocal Misc. Dates of materials: 1951-1982
  - Villa-Lobos/Weill [1961-1986] (Box 102)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Villa-Lobos, Heitor (1881-) (Complete Works; Biography; Villa-Lobos; Opera; Quintet; Opera; Orch. Misc.; Vocal Misc.; Song; Choral Misc.; Orch. Misc.; Tone Poem; Style; Complete Works; Overture, Prelude; Choros; Ballet; Quartet; Bachianas;Mass; Fantasia; Cello Misc.; Suite), 2.(Weill, Kurt) (Kurt Weill Newsletter; Opera; Song; Misc.; Weill; Symphony; Sinfonia; Musical; Cantata) Dates of materials: 1961-1986
  - Violinists [1963-1969] (Box 102)
    Content: Articles, Concert Programs Headings: A-Z articles and concert programs about violinists Dates of materials: 1963-1969
  - Vivaldi 1974 (Box 102)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: (Concerto; Vivaldi) Dates of materials: 1974
  - Vocalists A-G [1965-1985] (Box 103)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: A-G information on vocalists Dates of materials: 1965-1985
  - Vocalists A-M [1965-1968] (Box 103)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: A-M information on vocalists Dates of materials: 1965-1968
  - Vocalists H-P [1965-1984] (Box 103)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: H-P information on vocalists Dates of materials: 1965-1984
  - Vocalists Mc-Z [1966-1969] (Box 103)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: Mc-Z information on vocalists Dates of materials: 1966-1969
  - Vocalists Q-Z [1948-1985] (Box 104)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: Q-Z information on vocalists Dates of materials: 1948-1985
  - Wagner I [1961-1988] (Box 104)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Biography, 2.Bibliography, 3.(Complete Works), 4.Instrumental, 5.Literary, 6.Letters, 7.Misc., 8.Orch. Misc., 9.Overture, 10.Song, 11.Style, 12.Die Feen (EMPTY), 13.Hollander Dates of materials: 1961-1988
  - Wagner II [1929-1989] (Box 104)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Gotterdammerung, 2.Liebesverbot, 3.Lohengrin, 4.Meistersinger, 5.Misc., 6.Parsifal, 7.Rheingold, 8.Rienzi, 9.Ring, 10.(Siegfried) Dates of materials: 1928-1989
  - Wagner III [1966-1989] (Box 104)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Tannhauser, 2.Tristan, 3.Walkure Dates of materials: 1966-1989
  - Walton [1942-1983] (Box 105)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Capriccio, 5.Choral Misc., 6.Comp. Works, 7.Concerto, 8.Film Music, 9.Incid. Music, 10.Letters (EMPTY), 11.Literary (EMPTY), 12.March, 13.Mass, 14.Misc., 15.Opera, 16.Oratorio, 17.Orch. Misc., 18.Overture, 19.Partita, 20.Quartet (EMPTY), 21.Sinf,. Conc., 22.Sonata (EMPTY), 23.Song, 24.Style, 25.Symphony, 26.Te Deum (EMPTY), 27.Toccata (EMPTY), 28.Transcription, 29.Variation Dates of materials: 1942-1983
  - Weber [1968-1984] (Box 105)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Aria, 2.Bibliography, 3.Biography, 4.Cantata (EMPTY), 5.Chamb. Music (EMPTY), 6.Choral Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Comp. Wks (EMPTY), 8.Concerto, 9.Dance, 10.Instr. Misc., 11.Incid. Misc., 12.Letters (EMPTY), 13.Literary, 14.March (EMPTY), 15.Mass (EMPTY), 16.Misc., 17.Opera, 18.Orch. Misc., 19.Overture, 20.Piano Misc., 21.Quartet (EMPTY), 22.Quintet (EMPTY), 23.Sonata, 24.Song (EMPTY), 25.Style, 26.Symphony (EMPTY), 27.Trio, 28.Variation Dates of materials: 1968-1984
  - Webern [1971-1982] (Box 105)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Orch. Misc., 2.Opera, 3.Instr. Misc., 4.Letters, 5.Literary, 6.Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Concerto, 8.Arrangements, 9.Bibliography (EMPTY), 10.Biography, 11.Cantata, 12.Choral Misc., 13.Comp. Works, 14.Passacaglia, 15.Piano Misc., 16.Quartet, 17.Quintet (EMPTY), 18.Sonata (EMPTY), 19.Song, 20.Style, 21.Symphony, 22.Theoretical (EMPTY), 23.Trio (EMPTY), 24.Variation Dates of materials: 1971-1982
  - Women Composers A-Ba [1967-1994] (Box 105)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: A-Ba information about women composers Dates of materials: 1981-1994
  - Women Composers B-Bl [1986-1993] (Box 106)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: B-Bl information on women composers Dates of materials: 1986-1993
  - Women Composers Bo-Bu [1974-1994] (Box 106)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs, Program Notes, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: None. Information on women composers with last names Bo-Bu in alphabetical order Dates of materials: 1974- 1994
  - Women Composers B-Z (Box 106)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Bauer, 2.Beach, 3.Gideon, 4.Larson, 5.Mallonee, 6.Zwilich Dates of materials: ?
  - Women Composers C-D [1975-1985] (Box 106)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: C-D information on women composers Dates of materials: 1975-1985
  - Women Composers E-F [1933-1991] (Box 106)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: E-F information on women composers Dates of materials: 1933-1991
  - Women Composers G-H [1975-1994] (Box 107)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: G-H information on women composers Dates of materials: 1975-1994
  - Women Composers Hi-K [1971-1992] (Box 107)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: Hi-K information on women composers Dates of materials: 1971-1992
  - Women Composers L [1986-1995] (Box 107)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: L information on women composers Dates of materials: 1986-1995
  - Women Composers M [1980-1994] (Box 107)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: M-Mc information on women composers Dates of materials: 1980-1994
  - Women Composers Misc. Articles 1975 (Box 107)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Amer. Music, 2.Bibliography, 3.Programs, 4.Women Dates of materials: 1975
  - Women Composers N-R [1981-1995] (Box 108)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: N-R information on women composers Dates of materials: 1981-1995
  - Women Composers S [1980-1993] (Box 108)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: S information on women composers Dates of materials: 1980-1993
  - Women Composers T-V [1988-1992] (Box 108)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: T-V information on women composers Dates of materials: 1988-1992
  - Women Composers W-Z [1985-1993] (Box 108)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: W-Z information on women composers Dates of materials: 1985-1993
  - World Music A-C [1989-1995] (Box 109)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Amish, 2.Appalachia, 3.Arabia, 4.Armenia, 5.Australia, 6.Austria, 7.Banjo, 8.Ballad, 9.Basque, 10.Belgium, 11.Bermuda, 12.Blues, 13.Bolivia, 14.Brazil, 15.Bulgaria, 16.Cajun, 17.Caribbean, 18.Civil War, 19.Colonial America, 20.Cowboys Dates of materials: 1989-1995
  - World Music S-Y [1991-1993] (Box 109)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Seafaring, 2.Shakers, 3.Spain, 4.Spiritual, 5.Sweden, 6.Switzerland, 7.Turkey, 8.War Songs, 9.Williamsburg, 10.World War II, 11.Vietnam, 12.Yugoslavia Dates of materials: 1991-1993
  - 1977 1977 (Box 109)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1977
  - 1978 1978 (Box 109)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1978
  - 1979 1979 (Box 109)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents, Articles Dates of materials: 1979
  - 1980 1980 (Box 110)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents, Articles Dates of materials: 1980
  - 1989 1989 (Box 110)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1989
  - 15th Century (Box 110)
    Contents: Lecture Notes, Musical Scores Dates of materials: ?
  - 17th-20th (Box 110)
    Contents: Notes, Articles Dates of materials: ?
  - 1969-64 [1960-64] (Box 110)
    Contents: Concert Programs of Baltimore Symphony Dates of materials: 1960-64
  - 1969-77 [1969-77] (Box 111)
    Contents: Concert Programs of Baltimore Symphony Dates of materials: 1969-77
  - 1977-78 [1977-78] (Box 111)
    Contents: Overture Magazine (of Baltimore Symphony) Dates of materials: 1977-78
  - 1979-80 [1979-80] (Box 111)
    Contents: Articles, Concert Programs Dates of materials: 1979-80
  - 1980-81 [1980-81] (Box 111)
    Contents: Baltimore Symphony Orchestra concert programs, publications Dates of materials: 1980-81
  - 1981-82 [1981-82] (Box 112)
    Contents: Baltimore Symphony Orchestra concert programs, publications Dates of materials: 1981-82
  - 1981-82 [1981-82] (Box 112)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1981-82
  - 1982-83 [1982-83] (Box 112)
    Contents: Concert Programs, Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1982-83
  - 1983-85 [1983-85] (Box 112)
    Contents: Articles about Baltimore Symphony Orchestra Dates of materials: 1983-1985
  - 1994-1995 Book I [1994-1995] (Box 112)
    Contents: Misc. documents (Annual summary) Dates of materials: 1994-1995
  - 1995-96 Book I 1995-96 (Box 113)
    Contents: Misc. Documents, Concert Programs Dates of materials: 1995-1996
  - 1995-96 Book II [1995-96] (Box 113)
  - Admin: RPT 1990 (Box 113)
    Contents: Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1990
  - Admin: RPT 1986 (Box 113)
    Contents: Misc. Documents Dates of materials: 1986
  - Admin 1994 (Box 113)
    Contents: Notes, Concert Programs, Correspondence, Scholarly papers Dates of materials: 1994
  - American Art (Box 114)
    Contents: Postcards of art established/made in America or with and American subject Headings: Alphabetical: C-Alexander Calder, John Singleton Copley, Currier; Ives, D-Stuart Davis, H-Aldro T. Hibbard, Henry Holiday, K-Wassily Kandinsky, L-John La Farge, P-Jackson Pollock, R-Norman Rockwell, Mark Rothko, S-Sargent, Adolf Sehring, T-John Trumbull, W-Benjamin West, Andrew Wyeth, Dates of materials: 18th-20th Century works
  - American Music I 1983 (Box 114)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Syllabi Headings: 1.Beginning, 2.Part I, 3.1986-7 (EMPTY), 4.Unlabled: American Music (17), 5.17th-18th (History), Woodwinds (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1983
  - American Music II [1987-88] (Box 114)
    Contents: Class records, Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Unlabled: Class Records, Overview of Am. Music, Misc. articles 2.Outlines Dates of materials: 1987-88
  - Ancient-Medieval: Term Papers I 1970 (Box 114)
    Contents: Scholarly Papers Dates of materials: 1970
  - Ancient-Medieval: Term Papers II 1970 (Box 114)
  - Ancient-Medieval: Unused Material I 1969 (Box 115)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Charts Headings: 1.Unlabled: Overview of Ancient-Medieval Music, Misc., 2.Southeast Asia, 3.Greece, 4.Rome Dates of materials: 1969
  - Ancient-Medieval: Unused Material II 1969 (Box 115)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Charts Headings: 1.Chant, 2.Ecclesiastical Drama, 3.Monophony Dates of materials: 1969
  - Anonymous Art (Box 115)
    Anonymous Art (Medieval) Contents: Postcards of Medieval Art Headings: 1.Medieval, 2.16th Century, 3.Baroque Dates of materials: 12th-18th Century European Art
  - Anthology I (Box 115)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Charts Headings: 1.Schering 2, 2.Smith College, 3.Soderlund (EMPTY), 4.Wolf, 5.Unlabled: Music Copied from Schering Dates of materials:?
  - Anthology II (Box 115)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.History of Music in Sound, 2.Jander, 3.Jeppsen, 4.Kinksy (EMPTY), 5.Norton, 6.Noyes (EMPTY), 7.Omnibus (EMPTY), 8.Schering Dates of materials:?
  - Anthology III (Box 115)
    Contents: Articles, Scholarly Papers Dates of materials: ?
  - Appreciation I 1992 (Box 116)